Guide to the Robert Y. Wing Electric vehicles (EV) collection, 1970-1997
Department of Special Collections
Robert Y. Wing Electric vehicles (EV) collection,
1970-1997
Special Collections M0980
Wing, Robert Y.,
9 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
An early member of the first chapter (Santa Clara Valley) of the Electric Auto Association, Bob Wing converted a '59 MGA Roadster in 1972. He has been the West Coast Editor of EV NEWS since it started in 1990. He is also an EV consultant.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Preliminary box listing available in Special Collections Reading Room and online. Accession 2001-224 (13.5 linear ft.) is not yet listed.The unprocessed portion of collection is not yet available for research.
Provenance
Gift of Bob Wing, 1998.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Bob Wing, 1998 and 2001.
Biography
An early member of the first chapter (Santa Clara Valley) of the Electric Auto Association, Bob Wing converted a '59 MGA Roadster in 1972. He has been the West Coast Editor of EV NEWS since it started in 1990. He is also an EV consultant.
Scope and Content
Serials (both U.S. and foreign), symposium proceedings, flyers, newsclippings, magazine articles, historical files, bibliography, etc.
Access Terms
Electric Auto Association of the Americas.; Automobiles, Electric.; Electric vehicles.; Elecric Vehicle News.; GLEAN; Green Car Journal.
Container List
- Alternative Transportation 1991-1992 (Box 1)
- ELFIRNytt (Sweden) 1992-1997 (Box 1)
- elfordons-Nytt (Sweden) 1995 (Box 1)
- Electric Vehicle News (later, GLEAN) 1990-1995 (Box 1)
- GLEAN (Great Lakes Electric Auto News) 1994 (Box 1)
- GLEAN/EV News 1995-1997 (Box 1)
- World Electric Transportation & Solar Explosion 1989-1993 (Box 1)
- Tucson Electric Vehicle Association 1994-1996 (Box 1)
- Electric Auto Assoc. Current Events 1991-1997 (Box 1)
- Electric Auto Assoc. News 1971-1991 (Box 1)
- Automotive News 1997 (Box 1)
- Electric Light and Power 1997 (Box 1)
- The Earth Times 1997 (Box 1)
- Green Car Journal 1997 (Box 2)
- Mobil E 1997 (Box 2)
- Power Delivery 1997 (Box 2)
- Utility and Telephone Fleets 1993-1997 (Box 2)
- Battieries International 1993-1997 (Box 2)
- Electric Vehicle Assoc. of the Americas (EVAA); symposium proceedings, handouts, photos, etc. (EVS 11) 1994 (Box 3)
- Electric Vehicle Pioneer News 1992-1993 (Box 3)
- Unique Mobility, Inc. nd (Box 3)
- U.S. Electric Car 1995 (Box 3)
- EVS 10; symposium proceedings 1990 (Box 4)
- EV Policy/Technology Conference 1992 (Box 4)
- WESCON/92 and WESCON/94 1992-1994 (Box 4)
- Phoenix APS 1992-1996 (Box 4)
- Other events, races, shows (handouts, etc) 1996 (Box 4)
- CALSTART Connection/Communications 1994-1997 (Box 5)
- Magazine articles 1990-1996 (Box 5)
- Newsclippings 1990-1996 (Box 5)
- Hybrids 1970-1980s (Box 5)
- Project California, Monitor report 1992-1995 (Box 5)
- Clippings 1980s (Box 5)
- Magazine articles 1980s (Box 5)
- Clippings 1970s (Box 5)
- Magazine articles 1970s (Box 5)
- Controller files 1973-1990 (Box 5)
- History file, 1805-1942 nd (Box 5)
- Bibliography and index 1979-1980 (Box 5)
- Denver Electric Vehicle Council (DEVC) Newsletter 1990-1997 (Box 6)
- Australian Electric Vehicle Assoc. Newsletter 1983-1996 (Box 6)
- Zero emission (Italy) 1995 (Box 6)
- Eco-Vehiculos (Spain) 1994 (Box 6)
- Electric Car 1994 (Box 6)
- Electric Grand Prix Corp. 1992-1995 (Box 6)
- Electrifying Times 1992-1996 (Box 6)
- Electric Vehicle Progress 1994 (Box 6)
- Electric Vehicle Assoc. of the Americas 1994-1995 (Box 6)
- Vancouver Electric Vehicle Assoc. (Canada) 1990-1997 (Box 6)
- EVA Hawaii 1992-1993 (Box 6)
- Electric Vehicle Development Corp. (EVDC) 1991 (Box 6)
- Utility & Telephone Fleets 1991-1995 (Box 6)
- Electric Vehicle Assoc. of Southern Calif. (EVAOSC) 1992-1997 (Box 6)
- Green Car Journal 1992-1994 (Box 6)
- Hydrogen Today 1995-1996 (Box 6)
- IEEE Spectrum 1992, 1995 (Box 6)
- Electric Auto Assoc., Las Vegas 1994-1997 (Box 6)
- MobilE (Germany) 1995-1997 (Box 6)
- MobilE (France) 1995-1997 (Box 6)
- NESEA; Northeast Sustainable Energy Assoc. 1991-1993 (Box 6)
- New Zealand Electric Vehicle Assoc. 1992-1996 (Box 6)
- Northern Olympic Peninsula Electric Cars 1993 (Box 6)
- Other EV newsletters 1991-1997 (Box 6)
- EEA - Phoenix 1997 (Box 6)
- EAAS - Sacramento 1992-1997 (Box 6)
- BAT - Battery Automated Transportation 1992-1996 (Box 6)
- 3 posters nd